freesupertips.co.uk 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy | Free Super Tips

About this privacy policy  
This policy sets out how we will use and share the information that you give us.

freesupertips is a trading name of Apsley Group International Ltd which is registered in England with company number 08774926 and has its registered office at 5 Fleet Place, London, EC4M 7RD. Apsley Group International Ltd is registered with the Information Commissioner’s Office under the Data Protection Act 1998; its registration number is ZA296667. When we refer to “we”, “us”, or “freesupertips” we are referring to this company.

You can get in touch with us in any of the following ways:

 **By email:  info@freesupertips.co.uk**

By post: Consumer Queries, Floor 7, Vivo Building, South Bank Central, 30 Stamford Street, London, SE1 9LS.

 **Who and what this privacy policy applies to**

This policy applies to individuals who have registered with freesupertips. This policy applies to the information about yourself that you choose to provide us with. This includes:

information you provide during the registration process, such as your name, and your contact details,

information you provide when you enter prize draws, quizzes, competitions or answer surveys, such as information about your lifestyle including your favourite sports, interests and gambling habits,

information which we may obtain about you from third parties (for example, because you have given third parties permission to share that information with us), information we collect about how you use the website.

 **Our obligations**

We are a data controller in relation to the information that you provide us with. As a result, we are legally responsible for how that information is handled.

We will comply with the Data Protection Act 1998 in the way we use your personal data. Among other things, this means that we will only use your personal data:

  * fairly, lawfully and transparently,
  * as set out in the legislation and this policy,
  * to the extent necessary for these purposes.

We may process your personal data ourselves or through data processors who will process data on our behalf. If we use data processors, we will remain responsible for ensuring that they comply with this policy and data protection law.

We will take every reasonable precaution to safeguard the personal information that you supply.

If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries about our privacy policy, website or service, please contact us using the details given above.

 **What we will use your data for**

We may use your information to provide you with information or newsletters that you have requested.

Where you have subscribed to our newsletter or have entered a competition you would have consent to us processing your data by submitting your personal data on this site, whether in those elds marked mandatory or otherwise.

You are afrming your consent for such information to be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You will be able to withdraw that consent at any time by the methods described below.

By continuing to use this website you have consented to information being collected from your device by cookies or other similar technologies, for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, including the display of targeted advertising based on the information provided.

 **Opting out at a later date**

Once you have given your consent, you can however still control whether or not you continue to receive communications. You can unsubscribe from receiving e-mail marketing or newsletter communications by using the instructions in any email communication we send you which will be an ‘unsubscribe‘ or ‘STOP‘ link.

 **Legitimate Interests**

We have a legitimate interest to process this data for the general running of our business including for transfer to our processors and for analysis.

 **Retention and destruction of personal information**

We will take reasonable steps to ensure the accuracy of the information we hold about you. We will not use your personal information unless it is (to the best of our knowledge) accurate and up to date.

We will not keep your personal information for longer than necessary. Once it has been decided that the information is no longer needed, it will be deleted promptly. Typical timescales are shown below.

  * for newsletters this will normally be three months after you have unsubscribed from these newsletters.
  * for competitions this will normally be six months following the end of the competition.

 **Your choices in relation to personal information**

You have the right to:

  * obtain access to your personal information,
  * receive information about us and the purposes for which we process your personal data,
  * The right to port your information to another service or to yourself
  * prevent processing which may cause you damage or distress,
  * object to direct marketing,
  * ask us to correct any errors or delete the information we hold, opt out of further contact.

If you would like to amend or delete your details or contact us in relation to the use of your personal information, please contact using this email: info@freesupertips.co.uk

 **Disclosure of your information**

We may process your personal data ourselves or through data processors who will process data on our behalf. These organisations may fall into the following categories;

  * marketing agencies who help us promote ourselves or deliver our services,
  * e-mail service providers who help us to send our newsletters and communications with you have requested from us.

If our business (or a signicant part of it) is offered for sale, your personal information may be given to the prospective buyer, who will be able to use it to help them evaluate the proposed sale. If the sale is completed, the buyer will be able to continue using your information in accordance with this privacy policy.

We will also disclose your personal data if we are under a legal obligation to do so.

 **International transfer**

We will not transfer your personal data outside of the EEA.

 **Security**

Unfortunately, the transmission of data over the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its security. Once we have received your data we will use strict security measures to try to protect it against loss, misuse, or unauthorised alterations.

We will also require any third parties with whom we share your information to keep the information secure.

 **Cookies**

We collect anonymous statistics regarding each user’s visits, such as which pages on the website were viewed and for how long. This information can’t be linked back to any specic individual and is collected via Google Analytics. If you wish to opt out of Google Analytics you can do so here, or you can learn more about it here.

Facebook and Twitter may use cookies to track that you are logged in and allow for sharing of our articles. We do not have any access to this information. You can congure your advertising preferences on social media such as Facebook, Twitter, Instagram or Pinterest by accessing your settings or preference options on the relevant platform.

Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. For more information on this, and more information about cookies in general, you may wish to visit www.aboutcookies.org. For information about how to delete cookies from your mobile phone you will need to refer to your handset manual. Please be aware that restricting cookies is likely to impact on your ability to use our website effectively and may make areas of our website inaccessible or inoperable.

If you no longer want to receive personalized advertising on any website you visit, you can usually opt-out directly through the privacy policy of the particular website you are accessing. Please note that this will not block ads that are displayed on the websites you visit, it will simply stop you receiving advertising that has been tailored to your interests. This opt-out relies on a cookie, so if you wipe all your cookies then that website will no longer know that you have opted out. The same applies if you use a different internet browser, or use a new computer to access the internet. You can also opt-out of such advertising by visiting the IAB opt-out platform at www.youronlinechoices.com. Please note that this and other platforms allow you to optout of interest-based advertising delivered by registered members.

The cookies we use are as follows:

 **Name Purpose More Information**

Google Analytics we use Google Analytics for tracking purposes

Twitter Analytics we use Twitter Analytics for tracking purposes

Sumo Analytics we use Sumo for tracking purposes

Cloudare Security, cache storage Cloudare cookies help optimise the website  and maintain security

cookieFB holds the ID of a featured bet used to perform a check to see if the user has  already seen and closed the featured bet modal seen

Offers stores an array containing bet used to display a notification of bets that the  ID’s that the user has user hasn’t seen previously seen

 **Whatsapp**

We use a 3rd party provider to provide WhatsApp messages. Your data will never be shared or sold and you will be unsubscribed if you message and say stop. Inactive users will be removed from our list after 1 year or on request.

 **Changes**

We may change the terms of this privacy policy from time to time. Any changes will be posted on this page.

 **Contacting us, exercising your information rights and complaints**

If you any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, wish to exercise your information rights in connection with the personal data you have shared with us or wish to complain, please contact:

By email: info@freesupertips.co.uk

By post: Consumer Queries, Floor 7, Vivo Building, South Bank Central, 30 Stamford Street, London, SE1 9LS.

You also have the right to complain to the Information Commissioner’s Ofce if you believe we have not acted within the law or have infringed your rights.

https://ico.org.uk/for-the-public/

https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/
